[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "While the seed kernels of this plant are a rich source of vitamin E and its sprouts are highly nutritious, its petals are poisonous. The kernels are used for the production of oil.", "correct_answer": "Sunflower", "incorrect_answers": ["Briar", "Honeysuckle", "Tulip"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Paul W.S. Anderson wrote, produced and directed all 3 Resident Evil movies.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the common name of the Quoll, a carnivorous marsupial native to Australia and Papua New Guinea?", "correct_answer": "Native cat", "incorrect_answers": ["Native rat", "Native fox", "Native dog"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following medications is effective for both depression and anxiety?", "correct_answer": "Paxil (paroxetine)", "incorrect_answers": ["Buspar (buspirone)", "Xanax (alprazolam)", "Wellbutrin (bupropion)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Blazing Saddles, when Mongo comes to town, a man says to him You cant park that animal over there. Its illegal. What is Mongos next move?", "correct_answer": "He punches the horse the man is sitting on.", "incorrect_answers": ["He pulls the guy off the horse and proceeds to belt him up.", "He abuses the man.", "He totally ignores the man and proceeds to smash up the saloon."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first  female  President of the Philippines?", "correct_answer": "Corazon Aquino", "incorrect_answers": ["Eleanor Concepcion", "Louiza Rizal", "Ramona  Magsaysay"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What characteristic sound does Darth Vader from the Star Wars movie series produce?", "correct_answer": "Heavy breathing", "incorrect_answers": ["Buzzing", "Screeching", "Hissing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Perry Mason won his cases. Week after week this D.A. lost to Perry on the TV show.", "correct_answer": "Hamilton Burger", "incorrect_answers": ["Billy Flynn", "Richard Brooks", "Ted Buckland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did the events in the fictional film The Blair Witch Project take place?", "correct_answer": "1994", "incorrect_answers": ["1990", "1984", "1987"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Mel Brooks film is not on the American Film Institutes list of 100 funniest American films?", "correct_answer": "High Anxiety", "incorrect_answers": ["The Producers", "Young Frankenstein", "Blazing Saddles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which member of the Wayans family composed the original music for the television series My Wife and Kids?", "correct_answer": "Dwayne", "incorrect_answers": ["Nadia", "Kim", "Damon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2005, Katrina became the strongest hurricane on record in the Atlantic Basin with a pressure of 882 millibars breaking the old record set by Gilbert (888 mb) in 1988.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]